

Christian Ramos

BLOCKCHAIN & WEB DEVELOPER

Details

Linkedin profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-ramos-a3b204229/

Phone: +18596674314

Email: superdev729@gmail.com Skype:live:.cid.e349ab3d4be911c9 Telegram: @CryptoDev729 Discord: CryptoDev#6040

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH
1995.07.29

Skills

Fast Learner

Hard worker

Computer Skills

Team Player

Excellent Communication Skills

Leadership and Teamwork

Good time management skills

Always on time

Flexible schedule

Blockchain tech

Web3.js

Solidity

Hardhat/truffle

Ether.js

Profile

I am a Full-Stack Developer with a strong knowledge base and 7+ years of experience in developing Websites and Web-Based Systems.

I have worked as blockchain full stack Developer in multiple crypto startups, projects related to NFT, Defi, Dapp, Betting games.

I am a life-long learner and is looking forward to working on exciting and challenging projects. I am continuously trying to improve, learn more and gain new experiences. Recently, I have been working mostly Solana blockchain

Employment History

Senior Blockchain Developer at Midgard, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2020 — OCTORBER 2021

- NFT marketplace on several network such as BSC, Ethereum, Polygon and etc.
- Trading Bot with strong strategies (Front-running, Snipping, Arbitrage, Contract Bot)
- Smart contract development
- Several DEX platforms (Pancakeswap, Uniswap and etc) Fork
- · New token development with profitable Tokenomics
- Developed several Dapp project such as Staking, Lottery, Vesting and etc.
- · Yield Farming protocols and Liquidity Mining protocols
- P2P/Pool Lending and Borrowing
- New token deployment based on ERC20, ERC721, ERC1155, BEP20, BEP721, BEP1155
- · Multichain Web and Mobile wallet
- · NFT Game Development
- Dapp Customization

Senior Python Developer at Symph, Philippines

JANUARY 2017 — NOVEMBER 2018

- Developed AI chat bot with NLP using python, and implemented OCR model
- Developed web application back-end components while communicating with 30+ clients to identify their needs/goals and work on meeting them
- Consumed APIs while utilizing Python requests to read numerous JSON reports and file automatic bugs in the NVBugs for intermittent test
- Collected massively data from several sources to make website database
- Developed ETL scripts in Python to get data from one database table and update the resultant to another
- Used Python and Django to interface with the jquery UI, managing the storage and deletion of 50+ content
- Acquired in-depth knowledge in relational databases, ontologies, and linked data. Implemented a classification model written in Java, that automatically categorizes Wikipedia pages as either belonging to the

Several Network Experiences

JAVASCRIPT Frameworks

PHP Frameworks

Python & AI

Languages

English

Filipino

Hobbies

Market Researching, Gaming, Sports

- topic "Food and Drink" or not
- Built prototypes for training word-vectors embeddings and graph embeddings

Senior Software Engineer at UPWORK

JANUARY 2014 — NOVEMBER 2020

- Developed software applications involving web-based and native user interfaces and database interaction
- Contributing to process improvements in software development, project management, and quality assurance.
- Single-touch automation starts with a shape file, generates layers of progressively-smaller polygon grids, converts the coordinate reference system, and deploys the millions of spatial data points to Amazon RDS.
- Fully modern web development stack: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, AngularJS, React, Node.js, Vue, etc.
- Developed a blockchain explorer and cryptocurrency accounting system for Bitcoin and Ethereum.
- Implemented a method for efficiently tracking the flow of funds between different addresses.
- Deployed the system on Digital Ocean using Docker.
- Used REST APIs and WebSocket APIs

Education

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, University of the Philippines Diliman

APRIL 2012 — MARCH 2015

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, University of London, UK JANUARY 2015 — OCTOBER 2015